CRUSADE WITH T.B. JOSHUA - Cali, Colombia
PRAYER TIME
The hour has come.
Are you ready?
Your deliverance is as close to you as your mouth.
Your healing is as close to you as your mouth.
Our word and prayer have tremendous power to destroy the power of darkness.
I command right now, those on the wheelchairs - right now I command you - get healed!
Get healed!
I command your fluids, I command your bones, I command your tendons, I command your blood,
to get ready to receive life!
Be healed!
[A woman is healed of difficulty in walking- She is no longer using a walker.]
In the name of Jesus Christ!
[A woman is healed of difficulty in walking - She is no longer using a walker.]
[Healed of difficulty in walking - She is no longer using a walker.]
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I say, walk, in the name of Jesus!
[Healed of difficulty in walking. No longer using a walker.]
[Clapping]
It is your day; it is your time - get healed! Be healed!
[Healed of difficulty in walking; no longer using wheelchair.]
Be healed!
[Healed of difficulty in walking; no longer using crutches.]
Right now, whatever sickness and disease - place your hand.
I say, be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Our word and our prayer have tremendous power.
In your bones, you sickness;
in the tendons, you sickness;
in the bones, you sickness, I command you right now - be healed!
[Healed of difficulty in walking; no longer using wheelchair]
[Healed of difficulty in walking; no longer using crutches.]
[Colombia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2]
Be healed!
That dark in complexion sister - walk now!
[Healed of difficulty in walking; no longer using crutches.]
Right now, those of you that need deliverance, it is time for your deliverance.
Every power that torments your life - I say, be delivered!
You witches and wizards, I say be delivered!
Witches and wizards, be delivered!
[Manifestation of evil spirits]
I command all spirits of witchcraft, all spirits of sorcery, all spirits of divination -
I command you out, in the name of Jesus!
Come out, I say, come out!
All spirits, all evil spirits, all spirits of witchcraft, witchcraft - I say, out!
[Manifestation of evil spirits]
Holy Ghost fire!
All spirits of witchcraft - I say out!
[Manifestation of evil spirits]
As Prophet T.B. Joshua continues to pray, the power of God storms the scene,
and people are being delivered from whatever sickness, and afflictions that have been tormenting their lives.
This is the proof that the Book of Acts is not mere history, but a pattern of what God wants His church to be.
Jesus Christ is still the same yesterday, today, and forever.
His power and effectiveness have not changed.
For where the power of God is, there is liberty, healing, and all of God's blessings.
[Vomiting poisonous substances]
[Manifestation of evil spirits]
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Vomiting poisonous substances]
You witchcraft, in the name of Jesus, get delivered!
I command you out - you witchcraft!
[Manifestation of evil spirits]
Those of you on the gallery, all spirits of witchcraft, all spirits of the past
that are hindering your present and your future -
come out of your life! I say, come out, in the name of Jesus!
[Manifestation of evil spirits]
I command every addiction, spirit of immorality, spirit of idolatry,
come out of your sexual character!
I say, come out - you spirit of immorality!
You spirit of idolatry, you spirit of addiction - I say, come out!
Come out of your sexual character, in the name of Jesus!
[Manifestation of evil spirits]
In the name of Jesus!
Fire, in the name of Jesus!
Hallelujah.
All spirits of addiction, witchcraft, divination, sorcery, immorality, lust -
I command them out from your sexual character!
I say, out! Out!
People are brought out from all corners of the stadium,
as the evil spirit entities disturbing their lives, cannot stand the light of God.
I command you out!
I say, out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
[Manifestation of evil spirits]
You have another chance, another opportunity.
Listen, don't let self-pity hold you back.
Now everyone here, the anointing is available and sufficient to set you free.
Jesus wants to heal you - I say, be healed!
What is your sickness?
Your word and prayer have tremendous power to destroy your sickness.
See the gentleman.
[Healed of difficulty in walking - no longer using wheelchair.]
I say, rise up right now!
Say to yourself, "Rise up, in the name of Jesus!"
In the name of Jesus!
Everyone here who is under the anointing and influence of my word,
I say, be healed! Be free!
[Healed of inability to walk - no longer using wheelchair.]
Be delivered! Your deliverance be as close as your mouth.
I say, be delivered!
Your deliverance is as close as your mouth.
I say, get delivered!
Your healing is as close as your mouth.
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
[Healed of difficulty in walking - no longer using wheelchair.]
Thank you Lord.
You can talk to God now.
Ask Jesus to be your Lord, the Lord of your life.
Ask Jesus to be your Redeemer.
Ask Jesus to be your Comforter.
Ask Jesus to be your Lord.
When Jesus becomes your Lord, your thinking becomes different; you think different.
Hallelujah.
Say, "I am healed, I am delivered, I am redeemed!"
Defeat and failure are things of the past!
I am born again!
Confess who you are in Christ Jesus right now.
Open your lips and begin to confess it!
Colombia Crusade With T.B. Joshua - Day 2
There is power in the name of Jesus
To break every chain
After the mass prayer, people still remain under the influence of the Holy Spirit.
The real, forceful and authentic power of God continues to move mightily through the stadium.
For where the light of God is, darkness has no hiding place.
Many who possessed evil spirits began to manifest,
and those who were bound to their crutches for many years rose up and walked to the glory of God.
The lightning of God containing the resurrection power, flows through the stadium
as God Almighty restores them back to the original position He had created them.
There is power in the name of Jesus
To break every chain
[Healed of difficulty in walking. No longer using leg braces.]
Colombia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophesies, deliverances, sermons,
and testimonies from The Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.